Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII. Publications, 1971-2013; 12.25 Linear Feet in 28 manuscript boxes; 6.01 Gigabytes in 377 computer files
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Urban and Community Commission Publications, 1979-1981 (Box 169, Folder 3, Box 312, Folder 16)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Where We Stand: Strategy and Resolutions of the New American Movement, 1977-1979 (Box 150, Folder 6, Box 313, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Women Organizing, 1978-1981 (Box 313, Folder 2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Women's Newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 150, Folder 7, Box 313, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Working Papers, 1971-1976 (Box 313, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- The Workplace Newsletter and Working Papers: Workplace Experiences of Members of the New American Movement, 1972-1973 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Working Papers on Socialism and Feminism, circa 1974-1978 (Box 150, Folder 9)
  - Newsletter of the NAM Caucus for a National Strategy, circa 1973 (Box 150, Folder 10)
  - Not Far Enough -- Drafts, Correspondence, and Issues, Summer 1981-Fall/Winter 1982/1983 (Box 150, Folder 11)
  - Not Far Enough -- Drafts, Correspondence, and Issues -- Incomplete, Spring 1984-Winter 1989 (Box 150, Folder 12)
  - Not Far Enough -- Incomplete, Summer 1990-Winter 1995 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Notes from the Grass Roots, 1977-1978 (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Nurses Caucus Newsletter, November-December 1982 and Summer 1983 (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Organize!, 1985-1987 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Organizing Resources -- General, 1996, undated (Box 343, Folder 10)
  - Our Struggle/Nuestra Lucha, 1978-1985 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Our Struggle/Nuestra Lucha, April 1986-November/December 1987 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Our Struggle/Nuestra Lucha, Spring 1988-Summer 1991 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Our Struggle/Nuestra Lucha -- Correspondence, Drafts, and Issues, 1992-1994 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Our Struggle/Nuestra Lucha -- Incomplete, 1996-1997 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Perspectives on Lesbian and Gay Liberation (Lesbian and Gay Taskforce), undated (Box 342, Folder 25)
  - Perspectives on Lesbian and Gay Liberation and Socialism, circa 1982 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Religious Socialism -- Incomplete, Spring 1977-Fall 1980 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Religious Socialism -- Drafts, Correspondence, and Issues, Winter 1981-Fall 1982 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Religious Socialism -- Correspondence and Issues, 1983-1984 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Religious Socialism, 1985-1986 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Religious Socialism, 1987-1988 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Religious Socialism -- Incomplete, Winter 1989/1990-Summer 1999 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Reproductive Rights Newsletter, June-Fall 1978 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Socialism and Sexuality -- Incomplete, April 1990-November 1991 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1979 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Forum, 1979 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Forum, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1981 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Forum, May 1981 (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Forum, May and October 1981 (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Forum, August 1982 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Forum -- Focus on DSA 1983 Convention -- Part 1 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Forum -- Incomplete, 1984 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Forum -- Incomplete, 1987-1988 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1989 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Forum -- Incomplete, 1989 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Issue, 1990 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1991 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Forum, Fall 1991 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Forum, Spring 1992 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Forum, Spring 1993 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Forum, Fall 1994 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Socialist Forum, 1995-1997 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Forum -- Correspondence and Drafts, 1997; TW_TAM_105_ER_118
  - Harrington, Michael, et al. -- A Socialist Perspective on the Politics of Poverty, 1987 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - West, Cornel, et al. -- Socialist Perspectives on Race, 1985-2001 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference Pamphlet Series, circa 1986-1987 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Socialist Standard, January-September 1983 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Standard, March 1984 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Socialist Standard, November 1984 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Standard, March-May 1985 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Socialist Standard, March-July 1986 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - Socialist Standard, March 1987 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Third World Socialists, 1984 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Toward an Economic Justice Agenda: Where Are We Now?, 2008; TW_TAM_105_ER_121
  - Delson, Robert -- Unilateral Reciprocated Nuclear Disarmament, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - What Is Democratic Socialism?, circa 1982-1983 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - What Socialism Is…And Is Not: Twelve Myths about Democratic Socialism, 1982-1989 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - "What's Wrong and Right with America" Manual, 1995; TW_TAM_105_ER_110
  - Where We Stand: A Political Statement of Democratic Socialists of America, circa 1982-1996
    - Drafts and Final Publication (Box 169, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_122
  - "Why Socialists Should Become Teachers", 2018 (Box 342, Folder 26)
  - Why We Are Socialists, circa 1982-1983 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Schiacchitano, Katherine -- Witness to Two Worlds: Salvadoran Refugees in Washington, 1987 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Women Organizing, 1981-1982 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Women Organizing, 1982-1983 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Working Papers, 1980-1993, undated (Box 169, Folder 11-12, Box 342, Folder 24)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Anti-Apartheid Leaflets and Statements, 1985-1987 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- A Better World in Birth, 1987 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Brochures, circa 1981-2010
    - Drafts and Final Publications (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_131
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Campus Bulletin, February 1974 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Chapter Organizing Manual, 2007; TW_TAM_105_ER_132
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Democratic Socialist Perspectives Pamphlets, undated (Box 341, Folder 11)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS)/Young Democratic Socialists of America (YDSA) -- Education Reader, 2013 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Electoral Strategy and Movement-Building Publications, circa 1988-2004 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Glossaries and Progressive Publications Guide, 1997-2005
    - Drafts and Final Publications (Box 170, Folder 7, Box 341, Folder 17)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_133
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Guide for High School Activists, circa 2000-2006
    - Paper Files (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_129
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Immigration Discussion Guide, circa 2006
    - Paper Files (Box 170, Folder 9)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_127
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- "An Incomplete Guide to the Radical Left in the United States", 2005; TW_TAM_105_ER_128
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Labor Support Organizing Manual -- Drafts, Correspondence, and Final Publications, 1983-1988 (Box 170, Folder 10-11)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Organizing Manual, 1974-2010
    - Various Drafts and Editions (Box 171, Folder 1-3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_126
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Organizing for Reproductive Freedom: Student Manual, 1986-1990 (Box 171, Folder 4, Box 341, Folder 13)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- "The Project on Student Debt" Packet, circa 2006 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Questions of Group Process, circa 1984 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- The Red Letter, 1997-2016
    - Correspondence, Drafts, and Issues (Box 171, Folder 7, Box 341, Folder 14)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_130
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Songs for Socialists, 1978-1987 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Socialism and Student Activism, 1986-1989 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Student Mobilization Against the Cuts Organizing Manual, 1982 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- "Student Reproductive Rights Organizing Manual", undated (Box 341, Folder 16)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Statements and Perspectives, 1987-2010
    - Drafts and Final Publications (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_134
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Study Guides and Reading Lists, circa 1985-2010
    - Paper Files (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_135
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Toolbox, 2008; TW_TAM_105_ER_136
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- We're on Our Way, Running: DSA Youth Section Tenth Anniversary Greeting Book, 1984 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Young Democratic Socialists (YDS) -- Which Way America? -- Original Publication and Revisions, 1981-1987 (Box 172, Folder 7-8)
- Series VIII. Chapters, 1971-2008; 26.06 Linear Feet in 56 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 folder in 1 shared box; 1.33 Megabytes in 30 computer files
  Arranged alphabetically by state, with administrative materials and regional chapters first.
  This series contains materials from local and regional chapters of DSA, from the time before the merger of DSOC and NAM through 2008. This series reflects the participation of members on a grassroots level and illustrates the importance of local organizing. Materials include reports, newsletters, conference programs, flyers, and correspondence. Also included are materials on regional events and in certain instances, such as in New York, California, and Illinois, chapter correspondence with state organizing committees.
  - "Bright Spot" Chapter Conversations, 2013-2014 (Box 342, Folder 6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Charters, 1972 (Box 313, Folder 6)
  - Chapter Anti-Harassment Infrastructure, 2019 (Box 342, Folder 7)
  - Chapter Evaluations, 1976-1980
    - NAM, 1976 and 1980 (Box 313, Folder 7-8, Box 314, Folder 1)
    - DSOC, 1977-1978 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Chapter Guidelines, circa 1978-1985
    - DSOC and DSA, circa 1978-1985 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - NAM, undated (Box 314, Folder 2)
  - Chapter Petitions, 1979-1983 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Chapter Reports, 1975-1993
    - NAM, 1975-1976 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1979-1993 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Chapter Resources, 1981-1999 (Box 342, Folder 8)
  - Chapter Surveys, 1973-1998
    - NAM, 1973-1975 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1983-1998 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Local Organizing Manual, 1989 (Box 342, Folder 9-10)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Travel Reports, 1971-1979 (Box 314, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Heartland Region, 1974-1983
    - NAM, 1974-1976 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - DSOC, 1975-1977 (Box 173, Folder 6-7)
    - NAM, 1977-1978 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - DSOC, 1978-1979 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1979-1981 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, circa 1980-1983 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Mid-Atlantic Region, 1982-1989 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Midwest Region, 1974-2003
    - NAM, 1974-1976 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1977 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1978-1979 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1999
      - Correspondence, Conference Programs, and Reports (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_143
    - DSA, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_144
  - New England Region, 1971-1981
    - NAM, circa 1971-1972 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1977-1981 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - NAM Northeast Region, 1974-1979 (Box 315, Folder 6-7, Box 316, Folder 1-2)
  - NAM Northern California Region, 1977-1978 (Box 316, Folder 3)
  - Northwest Region, 1976-1981
    - NAM, 1976-1979 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - DSOC, 1980-1981 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - NAM Rocky Mountain Region, 1977-1979 (Box 316, Folder 5)
  - Southern Region, 1974-1983
    - NAM, 1974-1977 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - NAM, 1978-1982 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1981-1983 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - NAM Southern California Region, 1975-1980 (Box 317, Folder 2)
  - NAM Southwest Region, 1977-1978 (Box 317, Folder 3)
  - Twin Ports (Duluth, Minnesota -Superior, Wisconsin), undated (Box 342, Folder 12)
  - Western Region, 1979-2003
    - Correspondence, Memos, and Reports, 1979-1994 (Box 174, Folder 8-9)
    - Electronic Records, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_149
  - Alabama, 1973-1983
    - DSOC and NAM, 1973-1974 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and NAM, 1975-1976 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - DSOC, NAM, and DSA, 1977-1983 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - NAM -- Rosa Parks Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 317, Folder 4)
  - Alaska, 1974-1979 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Alaska, 1980-1982 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Alaska, 1983-1989 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Alaska, 1992-1999 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Arizona, 1973-1981 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Arkansas, 1973-1975 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - California, 1972-1974 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - California, 1975 (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - California, 1976-1977 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - California, 1978-1979 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - California, 1980-1985 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - California, 1988-1991 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - California, 1992 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - California, 1993-1997 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - California -- Bay Area, 1972-1978 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - California -- Bay Area, 1979-1980 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - California -- Bay Area, 1981-1982 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - California -- Bay Area, 1983-1985 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - California -- Bay Area, 1986-1999
    - Correspondence, Newsletters, and Reports (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_137
  - California -- Bay Area, 2002; TW_TAM_105_ER_138
  - NAM California -- Berkeley, 1972-1974 (Box 317, Folder 5)
  - California -- Chico, 1974-1985
    - NAM, 1974-1978 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1985 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - NAM California -- East Bay, 1972 (Box 317, Folder 7)
  - NAM California -- East Bay, 1975 (Box 317, Folder 8)
  - NAM California -- East Bay, 1976 (Box 317, Folder 9)
  - NAM California -- East Bay, 1977-1979 (Box 318, Folder 1)
  - NAM California -- Fresno, 1972 (Box 318, Folder 2)
  - NAM California -- Harriet Tubman/Westside Chapter, 1976-1977 (Box 318, Folder 3)
  - NAM California -- Isla Vista, 1972 (Box 318, Folder 4)
  - California -- Los Angeles, 1972-1997
    - NAM, 1972-1973 (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - NAM, 1974 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - NAM, 1975 (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - NAM, 1976 (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - DSOC, 1976-1980 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1977-1981 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1981-1983 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1984-1986 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1987-1997
      - Correspondence, Newsletters, and Reports (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_139
    - DSA, undated (Box 342, Folder 13)
  - California -- Orange County, 1975-1985
    - NAM, 1975-1976 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1983-1985 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - NAM California -- Riverside, 1975-1978
    - Correspondence, Meeting Minutes, and Press, 1975-1978 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - Event Poster, 1976 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - California -- Sacramento, 1975-1978 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - California -- Sacramento, 1979-1984 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - California -- Sacramento, 1985-1989 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - California -- Sacramento, 1990-2000 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - California -- San Diego, 1975-1998
    - NAM, 1975-1976 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - NAM, 1977-1978 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1977-1979 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - NAM, 1979-1982 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1983 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1984-1989 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1991-1998 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - California -- Santa Cruz, 1977-1991
    - NAM, 1977-1982 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1991 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - California -- San Fernando Valley, 1976-2001
    - NAM, 1976-1979 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - DSA, 1988-2001 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - NAM California -- San Francisco, 1972-1981 (Box 319, Folder 8)
  - NAM California -- Santa Barbara, 1972-1979 (Box 319, Folder 9)
  - NAM California -- Santa Cruz, 1971-1981 (Box 320, Folder 1)
  - Colorado, 1972-1980 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Colorado, 1981-1985 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Colorado, 1993-2000 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - NAM Colorado -- Boulder, 1972-1981 (Box 181, Folder 4, Box 320, Folder 2)
  - NAM Colorado -- Denver, 1978-1980 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut, 1974-1991
    - DSOC and DSA, 1974-1991 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - NAM, 1976-1978 (Box 320, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut -- Hartford, 1982-1988 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut -- New Haven, 1972-1982 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Delaware, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Florida, 1973-2000
    - DSOC and DSA, 1973-1987 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1976-1977 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1996-2000 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Florida -- Miami, 1977-1985 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Georgia, 1972-2008
    - NAM, 1972-1977 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1973-1979 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-2008 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Hawaii, 1984 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Idaho, 1972-1988 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - NAM Illinois, 1972-1983 (Box 320, Folder 6, Box 182, Folder 9)
  - NAM Illinois -- Blazing Star Chapter, 1975-1981 (Box 183, Folder 3, Box 320, Folder 7)
  - Illinois -- Champaign-Urbana, 1977-1983
    - DSOC, 1977-1979 (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1979-1980 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - DSOC, 1980-1983 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Illinois -- Chicago Area, 1972-2005
    - NAM, 1972-1973 (Box 320, Folder 9)
    - DSOC, 1972-1974 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - NAM, 1974-1975 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - DSOC, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 5-6)
    - NAM, 1976 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - DSOC, 1976-1978 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1977 (Box 321, Folder 3-4)
    - NAM, 1978 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1979 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1979-1982 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - DSOC, 1980 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - DSOC, 1981 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1984 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - DSA, 1985-1988 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - DSA, 1989 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1990 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1991-1992 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1993-1995 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 1996-2005 (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - DSA, 2015 (Box 342, Folder 11)
  - NAM Illinois -- Lucy Parsons Chapter, 1980-1982 (Box 322, Folder 2)
  - NAM Illinois -- Mother Jones Chapter, 1975-1978 (Box 322, Folder 3)
  - NAM Illinois -- Sojourner Truth Organization, 1971-1977 (Box 322, Folder 4)
  - Indiana, 1973-2003
    - NAM, 1973-1974 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1974-1984 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - DSA, 1991-1995 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - DSA, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_140
  - Iowa, 1972-1998
    - DSOC, 1972-1979 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1973-1976 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1989 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 1990-1998 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Kansas, 1972-1988
    - NAM, 1972-1974 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - DSOC, 1973-1979 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1988 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Kentucky -- Central (Lexington)
    - NAM, 1972-1981 (Box 186, Folder 6, Box 322, Folder 8)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1985 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - DSA, 1986-1987 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - DSA, 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1990-1993 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky -- Louisville, 1973-1984 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Louisiana, 1973-1986
    - NAM -- New Orleans, 1973-1974 (Box 322, Folder 9)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1977-1986 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Maine, 1971-1989
    - NAM, 1971-1972 (Box 322, Folder 10)
    - DSOC, 1973-1979 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1989 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Maryland, 1973-1979 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Maryland, 1980-1983 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Maryland, 1984-1986 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Maryland, 1987-1989 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Maryland, 1991-1994 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - NAM Maryland -- Baltimore (Port City), 1971-1981 (Box 323, Folder 1)
  - NAM Maryland -- Baltimore (Port City), 1976-1981 (Box 188, Folder 4-5)
  - Massachusetts, 1972-1985
    - DSOC, 1972-1975 (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - DSOC, 1976-1978 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - NAM, 1976-1981 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1979-1985 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - NAM Massachusetts -- Amherst, 1972-1977 (Box 323, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts -- Boston Area, 1972-2001
    - DSOC, 1972-1974 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1972-1976 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - DSOC, 1975-1976 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - DSOC, 1977-1978 (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - DSOC, 1979-1981 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1984 (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - DSA, 1985-1988 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - DSA, 1989-1994 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1995-1997 (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - DSA, 2001; TW_TAM_105_ER_141
  - NAM Massachusetts -- Middlesex, 1973-1974 (Box 323, Folder 4)
  - NAM Massachusetts -- Middlesex, 1975 (Box 323, Folder 5)
  - NAM Massachusetts -- Middlesex, 1976-1978 (Box 324, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts -- Springfield, 1976-1983 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Michigan, 1972-1976 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Michigan, 1976-1979 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Michigan, 1980-1985 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Michigan -- Ann Arbor, 1974-1997
    - NAM, 1974-1978 (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1984 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1985-1997 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Michigan -- Detroit, 1972-2003
    - NAM, 1972-1981 (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1982-1984 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - DSA, 1985-1997 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - DSA, 2002-2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_142
  - NAM Michigan -- Red Cedar/Lansing, 1974-1979 (Box 324, Folder 5)
  - Minnesota, 1974-1996
    - NAM, 1974-1975 (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - DSOC, 1974-1977 (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1978-1980 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1981-1996 (Box 191, Folder 7)
    - DSA, 2000-2016 (Box 342, Folder 14)
  - NAM Minnesota -- Minneapolis, 1971-1977
    - Correspondence, Reports, Newsletters, and Press, 1971-1977 (Box 325, Folder 1-2)
    - Event Poster, 1972 (Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 19)
  - Mississippi, 1974-1982 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Missouri, 1974-1976 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Missouri, 1977-1990 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Missouri -- Kansas City, 1978-1988 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Missouri -- St. Louis, 1972-1991
    - NAM, 1972-1976 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1977 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - NAM, 1978 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - NAM, 1979 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1979-1991 (Box 192, Folder 5)
    - DSA, undated (Box 342, Folder 18)
  - Montana, 1974-1989 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Nebraska, 1983-1990 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - New Hampshire, 1972-1977 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - New Hampshire, 1978-1996 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey, 1972-1999
    - NAM, 1972 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - DSOC, 1974-1979 (Box 192, Folder 10)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1980-1988 (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - DSA, 1992-1999 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - New Mexico, 1973-1997
    - DSOC and DSA, 1973-1997 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1976-1977 (Box 326, Folder 3)
  - NAM New York, 1972-1976 (Box 326, Folder 4)
  - New York -- State Board of Representatives, 1983-1987 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - New York -- Albany, 1981-1989 (Box 193, Folder 5-6)
  - New York -- Buffalo, 1975-1985
    - NAM, 1975-1979 (Box 326, Folder 5)